

ABU HUZAIFA

Web And Graphic Designer

Address: B-112, Shaheen Bagh, Okhla 110025, New Delhi, Delhi, India

Phone: +91 6387869214

Email: abuhuzaifaw7@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Hello, I'm Abu Huzaifa. A frontend designer is highly motivated and has produced visually attractive and user-friendly websites after completing a 6-month internship. Skilled in Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript responsive design principles. Also I worked in graphic design

WORK EXPERIENCE

RS Top Coder Software Solution Company

June 2023 - June 2024

From June 2023 until June2024, I worked as a web designer and graphic designer.
Currently, I working

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Art in Geography, Sociology

Dr. Ram Manohar Lohia Avadh University, Ayodhya

July 2020 - Aug 2023

 Completed a Bachelor of Arts degree in Geography and Sociology with a strong focus on human geography, urban studies, and research methodologies. Developed a comprehensive understanding of how societies are organized spatially and how human behavior influences and is influenced by the physical environment.

Diploma in Computer Applications, Business Accounting, and Multilingual DTP

June 2022 - June 2023

National Institute of Electronics & Information Technology

 This CABA-MDTP one year Certificate course has been designed for transformation of Urdu speakers into productive human resources and making them part of the Employable Technological Work Force in the Emerging IT scenario and penetration of Computer Education to grass root level. The course contents have been enriched with

SKILLS

- Responsive Web Design
- User Experience (UX) Design
- · User Interface (UI) Design
- Graphic Design
- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript
- CorelDraw Creative Suite
- Adobe illustrator
- · Logo design, banner, and brochure
- Problem-Solving and Creative Thinking